<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[基于 JupyterLab 的比特币及速入门指南]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[进入区块链世界的绝佳入口]]></description>
        <link>https://bitcoin.doge.university/book</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 14:26:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://bitcoin.doge.university/book/sitmap.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <author><![CDATA[李大狗]]></author>
        <managingEditor><![CDATA[leeduckg@gmail.com]]></managingEditor>
        <webMaster><![CDATA[leeduckg@gmail.com]]></webMaster>
        <category><![CDATA[gitbook]]></category>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[比特币：一种点对点的电子现金系统]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Commerce on the Internet has come to rely almost exclusively on financial institutions serving as trusted third parties to process electronic payments. While the system works well enough for most transactions, it still suffers from the inherent weaknesses of the trust based model. Completely non-reversible transactions are not really possible, since financial institutions cannot avoid mediating disputes. The cost of mediation increases transaction costs, limiting the minimum practical transaction size and cutting off the possibility for small casual transactions, and there is a broader cost in the loss of ability to make non-reversible payments for non-reversible services. With the possibility of reversal, the need for trust spreads. Merchants must be wary of their customers, hassling them for more information than they would otherwise need. A certain percentage of fraud is accepted as unavoidable. These costs and payment uncertainties can be avoided in person by using physical currency, but no mechanism exists to make payments over a communications channel without a trusted party.]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoin.doge.university/book</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoin.doge.university/book</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[李大狗]]></dc:creator>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin: A Peer-to-Peer Electronic Cash System]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Commerce on the Internet has come to rely almost exclusively on financial institutions serving as trusted third parties to process electronic payments. While the system works well enough for most transactions, it still suffers from the inherent weaknesses of the trust based model. Completely non-reversible transactions are not really possible, since financial institutions cannot avoid mediating disputes. The cost of mediation increases transaction costs, limiting the minimum practical transaction size and cutting off the possibility for small casual transactions, and there is a broader cost in the loss of ability to make non-reversible payments for non-reversible services. With the possibility of reversal, the need for trust spreads. Merchants must be wary of their customers, hassling them for more information than they would otherwise need. A certain percentage of fraud is accepted as unavoidable. These costs and payment uncertainties can be avoided in person by using physical currency, but no mechanism exists to make payments over a communications channel without a trusted party.]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoin.doge.university/bookbitcoin_whitepaper_en.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoin.doge.university/bookbitcoin_whitepaper_en.html</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[李大狗]]></dc:creator>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin: A Peer-to-Peer Electronic Cash System]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Commerce on the Internet has come to rely almost exclusively on financial institutions serving as trusted third parties to process electronic payments. While the system works well enough for most transactions, it still suffers from the inherent weaknesses of the trust based model. Completely non-reversible（不可逆的） transactions are not really possible, since financial institutions cannot avoid mediating disputes（调节争端）. The cost of mediation increases transaction costs, limiting the minimum practical transaction size and cutting off the possibility for small casual transactions, and there is a broader cost in the loss of ability to make non-reversible payments for non-reversible services. With the possibility of reversal, the need for trust spreads. Merchants must be wary of their customers, hassling （麻烦）them for more information than they would otherwise need. A certain percentage of fraud is accepted as unavoidable. These costs and payment uncertainties can be avoided in person by using physical currency, but no mechanism exists to make payments over a communications channel without a trusted party.]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoin.doge.university/bookbitcoin_whitepaper_translated_words.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitcoin.doge.university/bookbitcoin_whitepaper_translated_words.html</guid>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[李大狗]]></dc:creator>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>